Build a web application bundle.

Global options:
-h, --help                  Print this usage information.
-v, --verbose               Noisy logging, including all shell commands executed.
                            If used with "--help", shows hidden options. If used with "flutter doctor", shows additional diagnostic information. (Use "-vv" to force verbose logging in those cases.)
-d, --device-id             Target device id or name (prefixes allowed).
    --version               Reports the version of this tool.
    --enable-analytics      Enable telemetry reporting each time a flutter or dart command runs.
    --disable-analytics     Disable telemetry reporting each time a flutter or dart command runs, until it is re-enabled.
    --suppress-analytics    Suppress analytics reporting for the current CLI invocation.

Usage: flutter build web [arguments]
-h, --help                                                   Print this usage information.
    --[no-]tree-shake-icons                                  Tree shake icon fonts so that only glyphs used by the application remain.
                                                             (defaults to on)
-t, --target=<path>                                          The main entry-point file of the application, as run on the device.
                                                             If the "--target" option is omitted, but a file name is provided on the command line, then that is used instead.
                                                             (defaults to "lib\main.dart")
-o, --output                                                 The absolute path to the directory where the repository is generated. By default, this is <current-directory>/build/<target-platform>.
                                                             Currently supported for subcommands: aar, web.
    --[no-]pub                                               Whether to run "flutter pub get" before executing this command.
                                                             (defaults to on)
    --build-number                                           An identifier used as an internal version number.
                                                             Each build must have a unique identifier to differentiate it from previous builds.
                                                             It is used to determine whether one build is more recent than another, with higher numbers indicating more recent build.
                                                             On Android it is used as "versionCode".
                                                             On Xcode builds it is used as "CFBundleVersion".
                                                             On Windows it is used as the build suffix for the product and file versions.
    --build-name=<x.y.z>                                     A "x.y.z" string used as the version number shown to users.
                                                             For each new version of your app, you will provide a version number to differentiate it from previous versions.
                                                             On Android it is used as "versionName".
                                                             On Xcode builds it is used as "CFBundleShortVersionString".
                                                             On Windows it is used as the major, minor, and patch parts of the product and file versions.
    --debug                                                  Build a debug version of your app.
    --profile                                                Build a version of your app specialized for performance profiling.
    --release                                                Build a release version of your app (default mode).
    --dart-define=<foo=bar>                                  Additional key-value pairs that will be available as constants from the String.fromEnvironment, bool.fromEnvironment, and int.fromEnvironment constructors.
                                                             Multiple defines can be passed by repeating "--dart-define" multiple times.
    --dart-define-from-file=<use-define-config.json|.env>    The path of a .json or .env file containing key-value pairs that will be available as environment variables.
                                                             These can be accessed using the String.fromEnvironment, bool.fromEnvironment, and int.fromEnvironment constructors.
                                                             Multiple defines can be passed by repeating "--dart-define-from-file" multiple times.
                                                             Entries from "--dart-define" with identical keys take precedence over entries from these files.
    --[no-]native-null-assertions                            Enables additional runtime null checks in web applications to ensure the correct nullability of native (such as in dart:html) and external (such as with JS interop) types. This is enabled by default but only takes effect in sound mode. To report an issue with a null assertion failure in dart:html or the other dart web libraries, please file a bug at: https://github.com/dart-lang/sdk/issues/labels/web-libraries
                                                             (defaults to on)

Flutter web options
    --base-href                                              Overrides the href attribute of the <base> tag in web/index.html. No change is done to web/index.html file if this flag is not provided. The value has to start and end with a slash "/". For more information: https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTML/Element/base
    --pwa-strategy                                           The caching strategy to be used by the PWA service worker.

          [offline-first] (default)                          Attempt to cache the application shell eagerly and then lazily cache all subsequent assets as they are loaded. When making a network request for an asset, the offline cache will be preferred.
          [none]                                             Generate a service worker with no body. This is useful for local testing or in cases where the service worker caching functionality is not desirable

    --[no-]web-resources-cdn                                 Use Web static resources hosted on a CDN.
                                                             (defaults to on)
-O, --optimization-level                                     Sets the optimization level used for Dart compilation to JavaScript/Wasm.
                                                             [0, 1, 2, 3, 4]
    --[no-]source-maps                                       Generate a sourcemap file. These can be used by browsers to view and debug the original source code of a compiled and minified Dart application.

JavaScript compilation options
    --csp                                                    Disable dynamic generation of code in the generated output. This is necessary to satisfy CSP restrictions (see http://www.w3.org/TR/CSP/).
    --dart2js-optimization                                   Sets the optimization level used for Dart compilation to JavaScript. Deprecated: Please use "-O=<level>" / "--optimization-level=<level>".
                                                             [O1, O2, O3, O4]
    --dump-info                                              Passes "--dump-info" to the Javascript compiler which generates information about the generated code in main.dart.js.info.json.
    --no-frequency-based-minification                        Disables the frequency based minifier. Useful for comparing the output between builds.

WebAssembly compilation options
    --wasm                                                   Compile to WebAssembly (with fallback to JavaScript).
                                                             See https://flutter.dev/to/wasm for more information.
    --[no-]strip-wasm                                        Whether to strip the resulting wasm file of static symbol names.
                                                             (defaults to on)

Run "flutter help" to see global options.
